

BRUNO FERREIRA

I'm a 18 years old youg boy with a long life ahead of me. A life that I hope will be full of challenges and enriching experiences that will allow me to envolve and reach my full potential. Never forgetting to enjoy the best that life has to offer with the people I love the most.

CONTACT

Porto, Portugal

+351 910 681 336

brunomgferreira17@gmail.com

brunomgferreira.github.io/mywebsite

EDUCATION

Bachelor | Informatics and **Computing Engineering**

Faculdade de Engenharia da Universidade do Porto

High School

Escola Secundária da Trofa

SKILLS

Profissional

Personal

- Project Management
 Time Management
- Leadership
- Creative Spirit
- Social Media
- Fast Learner
- Marketing
- Organized
- Data Analytics
- Purposeful
- Python

- Positive
- HTML/CSS Photoshop
- Friendly

INTEREST

- Football
- Sports
- Cars
- Motorcycles
- Motorsport
- Music
- Books

EXPERIENCE

2022 🛑 Junifeup - Marketing Department

Oct 2022 - Currenctly

I can't explain how proud I am to be part of one of the best junior companies in Portugal, and to belong to a dynamic and ambitious team that shares the same values as I do. In the marketing department I do several tasks such as:

- The planning, management and creation of content for JuniFEUP's digital channels;
- The idealization of JuniFEUP's Marketing strategy;
- Design of websites and mobile applications, and planning of the respective User Interface:

2021 - 2022

Vice President of the General Assembly of the Student Asociation

Oct 2021 - June 2022

I was part of the Student Association of Escola Secundária da Trofa in the academic year 2021/2022. I played a crucial role in the organization and execution of several projects and activities. It was a very enriching experience that allowed me to use my leadership and cooperation skills. In addition to my role as Vice President of the General Assembly, in this project I developed the logo for the student list and managed the social media of the association.

2020 - 2022

Restoration Project

June 2020 - Mar 2022

It took 2 years of daily work to leave a VW Golf Mk2 in an impeccable state, because "You either do it right, or do it twice". It was a very challenging project, but at the same time very enriching. I learned a lot. Not only hard skills, but also soft skills like time and resource management.

2019 - 2019

Liga Portuguesa Contra o Cancro

1 Nov 2019

It was a day spent raising money for the Liga Portuguesa Contra o Cancro.

2012 - 2022 🔵 Sports - Federated Football

Sept 2012 - July 2022

One of my biggest passions is sports, and that's why I have 10 years of federated football in my legs. I won many games and I also lost a lot of times, but above all I made friends and learned countless life lessons. Football taught me to be competitive and I learned not only to work as a team, but also to exceed my limits with work and discipline.